Meggy Final Project:
  I plan to do a rock-paper-scissors type game with the Meggy, using colors as the different elements. In my vision, I want the game to randomly produce 3-4 (not sure yet) colors, which the player has to immediately find the opposing colors to counter with. It is like a mix between rock-paper-scissors and Attack.
  The player can move around at the bottom of the screen between 3-4 slots, and enter the needed color (which can be selected by button A or B). The enemy colors will either come in waves, or by a count down timer. I think eight rounds (kept by the aux leds at the top) should be enough to exhaust the player. I don't intend for it to be infinite...
  I will need to create a way to make a "cursor" like thing that will switch between 3-4 colors. I will also have to find a way to get the enemies to come in a separate delay than the player's cursor (an array perhaps?). I will also need to keep score/levels with the AUX LEDS. There will probably be more things I will encounter, but this is what I can think of so far. I'm not sure how I will do them either, so I'm really just throwing out theoretical ideas here.  I know for a fact that I will struggle with the real-time aspect of the game. I will probably struggle with everything else as well. I'm quite concerned with the magnitude of this project. If anything, I will change the game to a singular rock-paper-scissors with only one slot. We'll see how it goes.